MOHAMED AMINE RHALLAB

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

www.medrhallab.com



www.medrhallab.com



581-999 (0687)



rhallab.dev@gmail.com



Quebec City, Qc, Canada

PROFILE

I am a Front-End developer who has a lot of experience in building interactive and responsive websites and web applications. I specialize mainly in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and VueJS. I also have experience with other JS frameworks and other programming languages!

SKILLS

- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript (ES6+)
- VueJs (2/3)
- jQuery
- REST APIs
- Responsive Web Design
- · Working in a scrum environment
- · Working with headless CMS
- Understanding a Design System
- · Great analytical Skills

EXPERIENCES

MAIN FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Insurance Journal (JDA) French Portal English Portal

May 2022 - Present

- Maintaining frontend on both the French and English platforms that supports a business modal inspired by SAAS.
- Replace the current Front-end architecture from Django to Vuejs
- Build new functionalities and improve current ones for a better user experience

Boite Beet Alfred CRH Canada

VUEJS FRONT-END DEVELOPER

October 2021 - April 2022

- Lead new web projects for big clients at the company
- Use of WordPress headless CMS for content integration with VueJs
- Create new reusable content for the UI-Kit used internally

EDUCATION

DEC IN WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

College limoilou 2018 - 2021

BAC IN MATHEMATICAL SCIENCES

Pythagore High School 2015 - 2018

FRONT-END DEVELOPER / IT PROJECT MANAGER

Freelancing / Consulting

March 2020 - March 2021

- Compliance with SASS and Front-End standards and conventions
- · Lead new web projects for multiple clients
- · Build new functionalities and improve current ones for a better user experience
- Translation of the design system into code while respecting each visual aspect of it (Responsiveness and Reusability of components)